A Guide to the Davis & Associates Architectural Drawing Collection, 1925-1985 (bulk, 1954-1985)
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Harrisonburg
  - Mini-Facility for Rockingham National Bank, 1976, 15 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Proposed Parking for Area Between S. Main St., Cantrell Ave, S. Mason St., and Grace St., 11 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Possible Office Expansion to Valley National Bank 1977, 5 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Preliminaries, 1961, 8 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Remodeling of 107 E. Water St for D. P. Davis, Jr./Fran-El Corp, 1975, 10 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Alterations to Rockingham Bank Annex Building, 1972, 6 Sheets (Box 9)
    Comm. #7207
  - New South Entrance for Harrisonburg Municipal Building, 1976, 15 Sheets (Box 9)
    Comm. #7611
  - Lucy F. Sims [sic] School, 1939, 1961, 9 Sheets (Box 10)
    Comm. #6101
  - Office and Manufacturing Plant for Electronic Specialty Co., 1963, 109 Sheets (Box 10)
    Comm. #6313
  - Phase II Addition to Space Conditioning, 1969, 38 Sheets (Box 10)
    Comm. #6828
  - Warren House, 1961, 85 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6108
  - (Remodeling) Traffic Court Room, City Police Dept, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6833
  - Alterations #2 for Harrisonburg Police Department, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6716
  - Holiday Hill Branch, First National Bank, 1966, 6 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6631
  - Plat of Earl H. Wetsel's Addition to the City of Harrisonburg, 1951, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Beam & Columns for Shenandoah Equipment Co., 1961, 2 Sheets (Box 11)
  - Harrisonburg Baptist Church, 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Proposed B. R. Addition, Mr. & Mrs. Z. D. Jackson, 1961, 5 Sheets (Box 11)
  - Northeast Harrisonburg Urban Renewal Area, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Proposed Office & Warehouse, Bob's Food Products, Inc., 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Garage & Porch Addn. Dr. & Mrs. W. H. Smith 1960, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Proposed New Building for Rockingham Milling, 1968, 7 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6732
  - Proposed Community Recreation Center, 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 11)
  - Brick Wall-Planter for 1st Presbyterian Church, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
  - Connecting Passageway for Denton's Stores, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6802
  - Cabinet Work, Mrs. Vera Conrad, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6803
  - Bathroom Remodeling, Mrs. Vera Conrad, 1969, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6910
  - Porch Remodeling for William Derr, 1969, 2 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6932
  - Addition to Spotswood Bank, 2 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6701
  - Remodeling for George Conrad Property, 1967, 6 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6709
  - A Branch Bank for First National Bank, 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 11)
  - Toilet Facilities for Harrisonburg City Recreation Dept., 1966, 1 Sheet (Box 11)
    Comm. #6621
  - Office Building for Stanley Turner, 1962-1965, 11 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #6302
  - Girls' Dormitory, Eastern Mennonite College, 1949, 4 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #4702
  - Terminal & Office Building, Smith Transfer Corp. 1961, 21 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6120
  - Terminal & Office Building, Smith Transfer Corp., 1961, 32 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6105
  - Shomo Residence, 5 Sheets (Box 11)
    Comm. #6509
  - Two Men's Dormitories for Eastern Mennonite College, 1962, 34 Sheets (Box 12)
    Comm. #6117
  - Entrance Addition to Administration Building, Eastern Mennonite College, 1968, 6 Sheets (Box 12)
    Comm. #6528
  - Campus High School Phase One for Eastern Mennonite College, 2 Sheets (Box 12)
    Comm. #6112
  - 1966Science Building for Eastern Mennonite College, 1966, 46 Sheets (Box 12)
  - Gymnasium, Eastern Mennonite College, 1957, 30 Sheets (Box 12)
    Comm. #556
  - Dutch Pantry Restaurant for the Shenandoah Investment Corp., 1971, 126 Sheets (Box 12)
    Comm. #7116
  - Hillandale Subdivision, 1962, 1964, 150 Sheets (Box 13)
  - Rockingham Milling Co., 1964, 1 Sheet (Box 13)
  - Mick or Mack #3 and Adjoining Building, 13 Sheets (Box 13)
    Comm. #6406
  - Proposed Alterations to Virginia Mennonite Home, 1970, 26 Sheets (Box 13)
    Comm. #6913
  - Housing Addition to the Richardson Building, Massanetta Springs Conference Center, 22 Sheets (Box 13)
  - Addition to Waterman Elementary School, 1981, 8 Sheets (Box 13)
    Comm. #8120
  - Office Addition to Rockingham Construction Co. (Main Offices), 1980, 1 Sheet (Box 14)
    Comm. #8004
  - Proposed Apartments, Scott-Neff, 1978, 3 Sheets (Box 14)
    Comm. #7823
  - Entrance Addition for Administration Building, 1966, 4 Sheets (Box 14)
  - New North Wing for Eastern Mennonite School, 12 Sheets (Box 14)
  - Renovation of the Administration Building at Eastern Mennonite College, 1978, 20 Sheets (Box 14)
    Comm. #7836
  - Alterations to Science Building at Eastern Mennonite College, 1979, 6 Sheets (Box 14)
    Comm. #7839
  - New Clubhouse for Spotswood Country Club, 1976, 58 Sheets (Box 14)
    Comm. #7418
  - Wheatley Development, 1972, 8 Sheets (Box 14)
    Comm. #7219
  - Additions to Spotswood Elementary School, 1974, 7 Sheets (Box 15)
  - Additions to Keister Elementary School, 1974, 40 Sheets (Box 15)
    Comm. #7410
  - Town and Country Motors, 1958, 23 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #5807
  - Franklin Heights, 1961, 69 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #5819
  - DNR, 12 Sheets (Box 16)
  - Low Rent Housing Project, 1 Sheet (Box 16)
  - Box Culvert over Blacks Run, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #6723
  - Rocco Building for Space Cond., 1969, 1 Sheet (Box 16)
  - Phase II Addition to Space Conditioning 1969, 32 Sheets (Box 16)
  - Weaver Property Development, 1974, 6 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #7409
  - Addition to Weaver Property Development, 1974, 2 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #7416
  - Mini-Warehouse Project for Weaver Properties, 1975, 5 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #7516
  - Revised Plot Plan, Harrisonburg Baptist Church, 1957, 1 Sheet (Box 16)
  - Office Expansion for Rockingham Milling Co., 1965, 1 Sheet (Box 16)
    Comm. #6534
  - Office Building for Rockingham County, 1967, 11 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #6729
  - Sales Facility and Corporate Offices for Valley Blox, Inc., 1983, 22 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #8223
  - Office Building for Keeler and Phibbs, 1970, 15 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #6942
  - Wheatley-Yeltzer Ford, 1968, 27 Sheets (Box 16)
    Comm. #6813
  - Harrisonburg City Maps, 13 Sheets (Box 16>)
  - Fire Station No. 1 and Rescue Squad, 1969, 36 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Addition to the Rockingham National Bank, 1965, 9 Sheets (Box 17)
    Comm. #6517
  - Science Building for Eastern Mennonite College, 1965, 3 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Addition to Administration Building, Eastern Mennonite College, 2 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Plant and Office Building for Kawneer Company, 1969, 2 Sheets (Box 17)
    Comm. #6922
  - Proposed Building Addition for Friendship Industries, 1980, 6 Sheets (Box 17)
    Comm. #7834
  - Floor Pattern, Store "B", Laundrymat, 1 Sheet (Box 17)
  - Proposed Motel, Massanetta Springs, 1976, 2 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Mick or Mack Store 1955, 39 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Campus High School Phase I for Eastern Mennonite College, 1963, 47 Sheets (Box 17)
    Comm. #6118
  - Addition & Alterations to the Eastern Mennonite High School 1972, 13 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Addition to Office Building of Winston Weaver 1978, 1 Sheet (Box 17)
    Comm. #7830
  - Port Road Office for the Spotswood Bank, 1968, 31 Sheets (Box 17)
    Comm. #6801
  - Various Additions to Massanetta Springs, 1968, 10 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Resource Recovery Facility, 31 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Downtown Mall, 5 Sheets (Box 17)
  - Parking Deck--Elizabeth and Mason Streets, 1978, 22 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #7842
  - Additions to Voskuil Cottage, Sunnyside Presbyterian Home, 1983, 5 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #8224
  - Proposed Community Recreation Center, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
  - Mick or Mack Store 5520, 3 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Fallout Shelter Addition to WSVA Radio Station, 1965, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
    Comm. #6522
  - Proposed Additions-Alterations to WSVA Studio Facilities, 1969, 7 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Radio Building and TV Alterations for WSVA, 1969, 17 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #6928
  - Production Center for Shenandoah Valley Educational Television Corporation 1968, 44 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Showroom Remodeling for Lincoln-Miller, 1966, 6 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #7231
  - Proposed Hillside Motel for Golden Horseshoe Corp., 1969, 2 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Proposed Parking Garage, 1971, 2 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Proposed Clinic for Drs. Schlabach, 1972, 5 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #7201
  - Driver Apartments--S. Main Street, 1972, 5 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Alterations to Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Wm. R. Smith, 1973, 2 Sheets (Box 18)
  - 110 Newman Avenue Office 1973, 2 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Sheets
    Comm. #
  - Schewel's 1976, 9 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Additions-Alterations to Virginia Mennonite Home, 1976, 38 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #5812
  - Remodeling of Daily News Record Office, 1965, 4 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #6407
  - Alterations and Press Room Addition to the Daily News Record, 1969, 14 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #6905
  - Proposed Alterations to Daily News Record, 1972, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
    Comm. #7210
  - Addition to Daily News Record 1975, 6 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #7322
  - Remodeling of Existing Offices for the Daily News Record, 1980, 3 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #8022
  - Second Floor Addition to Daily News Record, 1982, 3 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #8219
  - Alterations and Additions to the Daily News Record, 1978, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
    Comm. #7822
  - Water Street Elevation, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
  - Addition to Myers Residence, 3 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Port Road Texaco and Restaurant, 2 Sheets (Box 18)
  - Bathroom Additions to Residence of Mr. and Mrs. F. O. Funkhouser, 3 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #7309
  - Sunnyside Presbyterian Home 1970, 1 Sheet (Box 18)
  - Distribution Center for Ray Carr Tires Inc., 1983, 35 Sheets (Box 18)
    Comm. #8215
  - Kavanaugh Housing for the Elderly 1977, 83 Sheets (Box 19)
    Comm. #7707
  - Transfer Print Company for Storey of Virginia, 1976, 60 Sheets (Box 19)
  - Additions & Alterations to Rockingham County Jail 1962, 2 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #6210
  - Factory Building for Wampler Chemical Corporation, 1975, 2 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #7525
  - Martin Palmer Property, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #7105
  - First Floor Plan, Rockingham National Bank, 1961, 5 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #7801
  - Proposed Offices for Computer Center, Rockingham National Bank, 1977, 3 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #7717
  - A. M. P. of Harrisonburg, 1977, 2 Sheets (Box 20)
  - Port Republic Property, Trout Enterprizes, 1980, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
  - Fire Practice Tower, 1979, 3 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #7910
  - Proposed Building for Walker Manufacturing Co., 1 Sheet (Box 20)
  - Addition to Richardson Building at Massanetta Springs, 1979, 12 Sheets (Box 20)
  - Additions & Alterations to Hotel-Richardson Bldg. & Auditorium, Massanetta Springs Inc. 1961, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #6012
  - Office Addition, Massanetta Springs Inc., 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #6731
  - Alterations & Addition to Rockingham County Jail 1967, 25 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #6602
  - Distribution Center for Ray Carr Tires Inc., 1983, 46 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #8213
  - Remodeling of Front, Schewel Furniture Co., 1956, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #5623
  - New Freight Elevator & Shaft for Schewel Furniture Co., 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #5821
  - Schewel Furniture Co. Remodeling for Colonial Shop, 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #5917
  - Canopy Alterations & Additions for Schewel's Furniture Co. 1964, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #6421
  - Modification to Schewel Furniture Store, 1968, 3 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #6817
  - Alterations to Schewel Furniture Store, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #7014
  - Alterations & Additions to Schewels Furniture Store, 1975, 28 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #7406
  - Miscellaneous plans for Schewels Furniture Co., 5 Sheets (Box 20)
  - J. C. Penney Co. Inc., 1956, 29 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #5525
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Lester B. Frank 1957, 8 Sheets (Box 20)
    Comm. #5707
  - Valley Blox, 1957, 1 Sheet (Box 20)
    Comm. #5713
  - Present Buildings for the Rockingham National Bank, 1957, 12 Sheets (Box 21)
  - Additions & Alterations for Rockingham Public Library, 1966, 18 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #6525
  - The Rockingham National Bank Drive-In, 1957, 18 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #5611
  - Sancar Corp. Second Floor Addition, 1957, 8 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #5703
  - Sancar Corp. Addition to Second Floor, 1958, 3 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #5835
  - Proposed Residence for Mr. & Mrs. P. F. Sowers, 1957, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
  - Present Choir Loft for Harrisonburg Presbyterian Church, 1957, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
  - Warehouse for Union Roofing & Paper Co., 1958, 15 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #5828
  - Addition to Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Chas. A. Hammer 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
    Comm. #5806
  - Crusher Foundation for Jamison Black Marble Co. Inc., 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
    Comm. #5822
  - Jamison Black Marble Co., 1959, 3 Sheets (Box 21)
  - Office Addition to Union Roofing Co., 1961, 2 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #6107
  - Hawkins Hardware Store, 1964, 19 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #6419
  - Computer Center for Rockingham National Bank (Reproduction Room), 1975, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
    Comm. #7513
  - Drive-Up Facilities for the United Virginia Spotswood Bank, 1977, 23 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #7313
  - Proposed Office Alterations for R. N. B. Center, 1978, 19 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #7812
  - Mezzanine Office Remodeling for RNB, 1984, 3 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #8401
  - Proposed West Avenue Office Complex, 1983, 11 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #8326
  - Bud-Dol Apartments, 1983, 7 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #8226
  - Porch Enclosure for Mr. & Mrs. D. P. Davis, Jr., 1 Sheet (Box 21)
  - Packaging Corp. of America, 1966, 18 Sheets (Box 21)
  - Remodeling for Mr. & Mrs. W. E. Wilburn, 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #6708
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. R. C. Williams, 1967, 8 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #6622
  - Balcony Redesign for Muhlenberg Lutheran Church, 1975, 2 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #7522
  - Addition to Wilburn Residence, 1977, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
    Comm. #7725
  - Renovation & Addition for Vepco Office, 1980, 23 Sheets (Box 21)
    Comm. #8011
  - Proposed Medical Office Building for Triton Development Inc., 1981, 1 Sheet (Box 21)
    Comm. #80116
  - Schemes (1a, 1b, 2b) for Joe Miller, 5 Sheets (Box 21)
  - Wheatley-Yeltzer Ford, 1968, 27 Sheets (Box 22)
  - College Court Apartments, 1962, 4 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Oak Hill Apartments, 1962, 9 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #6215
  - Proposed Shenandoah Lodge Expansion, 1980, 27 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #8020, 8022
  - Davis & McClintock Office, 6 Sheets (Box 22)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 22)
  - Plot Plan for Mr. Joe Mintzer, 1960, 7 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Simmers Plot 1960, 3 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Court Square Springhouse, 1977, 21 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment of the J.C. Penney Building (Court Square Village), 1979, 20 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #7850
  - Property Owned by The Valley Hardware Co. Inc, 1 Sheet (Box 22)
  - Harrisonburg City Topo Map, 1 Sheet (Box 22)
  - School Bus Garage and Shop Building for Rockingham County School Board, 1959, 3 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5903
  - Valley of VA Co-op Milk Producers Assn. Inc., 3 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5621, 5622
  - Alterations to Cavalier Poultry Corp., 1957, 5 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5626
  - Bethel Temple 1963, 11 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #6309
  - Alterations & Addition to West Rockingham Mutual Building 1967, 2 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Cloverleaf Shopping Center, 1961, 7 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Sipe Building, 1956, 5 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5613
  - F. W. Woolworth Co. Store No. 1296, 1956, 34 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5605
  - Youth Center for City of Harrisonburg, 1957, 8 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #5706
  - Cabana, Bath House, & Garden for Mr. & Mrs. Fred O. Funkhouser 1960, 17 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #6005
  - Addition to Valley Bowling Center Inc., 1960, 5 Sheets (Box 22)
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. M. T. Brackbill "Starrywood" 1961, 10 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #6009
  - Canopy for Grottoes Branch, Rockingham National Bank, 1979, 9 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #7901
  - Gamby Distributing Co. Inc, 1978, 9 Sheets (Box 22)
    Comm. #7826
  - Harrisonburg City Maps, 13 Sheets (Box 22)
- Rockingham County
  - Proposed High School for Rockingham County (Massanutten Site), 1972, 9 Sheets (Box 23)
    Comm. #7226
  - Additions & Alterations to John Wayland Intermediate School, 1975, 59 Sheets (Box 23)
    Comm. #7510>
  - Additions and Alterations to John C. Myers Intermediate School, 1975, 2 Sheets (Box 23)
    Comm. #7426
  - Metro Pants Co., 1969, 1 Sheet (Box 23)
  - Topographical Survey of Lot 518, Unit 4, Massanutten Development Company, 1982, 1 Sheet (Box 23)
  - Activities Building for McGaheysville Fire Company, 1979, 79 Sheets (Box 23)
    Comm. #7715
  - Ski Shop for Massanutten Village, 1977, 8 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #7721
  - Proposed Broadway-Timberville Elementary School, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #7007
  - McGaheysville Elementary School, 1968, 9 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6804
  - Addition to Pleasant Valley Elementary School, 1966, 18 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6624
  - Pleasant Valley Elementary School, 1962, 41Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6201
  - Manufacturing Plant for Spotswood Industries, 1958, 10 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5801
  - John C. Myers Intermediate School, 1962, 1 Sheet (Box 24)
    Comm. #6205
  - Fulks Run Elementary School, 1960, 2 Sheets (Box 24)
  - Addition to Turner Ashby High School, 1959, 7 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5817
  - Addition to Turner Ashby High School, 1962, 11 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6123
  - Addition and Alterations to Elkton Manor Home for Adults, 1981, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #8119
  - Bridgewater Office for the Rockingham National Bank, 1971, 1 Sheet (Box 24)
    Comm. #7106
  - Proposed Addition to First Church of God, 2 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #7848
  - Metro Pants Distribution Center, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 24)
    Comm. #7624
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. E. N. Early, 4 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5816
  - An Addition to a Residence for Mr. & Mrs. George Bryan Jr., 1960, 4 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6008
  - Service Station for Rockingham Farm Bureau, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5211
  - Addition to Bridgewater/John Wayland Intermediate School, 1969, 7 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6902
  - Addition to Broadway High School, 1959, 7 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5818
  - Proposed Addition to the Branch Bank of the Valley National Bank, 1 Sheet (Box 24)
    Comm. #7113
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Fred Wampler, 1959, 15 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5830
  - Additions to Mill Building, Beacon Milling Co., 1960, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #6104
  - Addition to Beacon Milling Company, 1958, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5824
  - Office Building for Beacon Milling Co., 1956, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5619
  - Existing Mill & Warehouse and Additions & Alterations, Beacon Milling Co., 1956, 27 Sheets (Box 24)
    Comm. #5624
  - Additional Soft Feed Storage Bins--Beacon Milling Co., 3 Sheets (Box 24)
  - New Bins for Beacon Milling Co., 1963, 1 Sheet (Box 24)
    Comm. #6311
  - Beacon Milling Co. Miscellaneous, 3 Sheets (Box 24)
  - Suggested Library Addition, Broadway High School, 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 25)
  - Addition to Turner Ashby High School, 1959, 11 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Addition to Keezletown Elementary School, 1960, 19 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #6002
  - Fulks Run Elementary School, 1960, 17 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Addition, Valley National Bank Branch, 1971, 21 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Branch Bank for Valley National Bank, 1968, 11 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #6714
  - Dayton Mennonite Church, 1982, 11 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #8139
  - Dayton Mennonite Church, 4 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #7405
  - Addition to the School Bus Garage and Shop Building, 1978, 2 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #7829
  - Harrisonburg Office of the Planters Bank, 1971, 19 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #7108
  - Addition to Pleasant Valley Elementary School, 1966, 16 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Proposed Additions-Alterations to Broadway High School, 1982, 24 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #8201
  - Addition & Alterations to Turner Ashby High School, 1982, 16 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #8142
  - Elkton Intermediate & High School, 5 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Port Republic Elementary School, 4 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Montevideo Intermediate and High School, 7 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Addition No. 2 to John Wayland Intermediate School, 1976, 2 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #7510
  - Proposed Additions-Alterations to John Wayland School, 1982, 5 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #8122
  - Miscellaneous Rockingham County Schools Enlarged Plans, 7 Sheets (Box 25)
  - Addition to Pleasant Valley Elementary School, 1966, 1 Sheet (Box 25)
  - Addition to Mt. Clinton Elementary School, 1966, 29 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #6626
  - The Planters Bank of Bridgewater, 1976, 6 Sheets (Box 25)
    Comm. #7623
  - The H. D. Lee Co. (Rockingham County Branch), 1 Sheet (Box 26)
  - Eastside (Spotswood) High School, 1978, 145 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #7629
  - Sunnyside Superintendent's Home, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 26)
  - Residence of Dr. M. E. Myers, 1955, 2 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #5527
  - Mutual Feed Co. 1958, 1 Sheet (Box 26)
    Comm. #5805
  - Elkton Elementary School, 1972, 20 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #6929
  - Fellowship Hall Addition for the Donovan Memorial United Methodist Church, 1973, 9 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #7211
  - Briery Branch Community Center, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 26)
    Comm. #7613
  - Eastside (Spotswood) High School, 1979, 7 Sheets (Box 26)
  - Plant Addition for Tru-Kut Door Corp., 1982, 1 Sheet (Box 26)
  - Dayton Mennonite Church, 4 Sheets (Box 26)
  - Proposed Facility for Raub Supply Co./Proposed Warehouse for Triton Development Inc., 1981, 7 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #8111
  - Proposed Residence for Mrs. Margaret Mundy, 1982, 3 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #8200
  - School Sign for Rockingham County School Board, 1965, 1 Sheet (Box 26)
  - Driver Training Facility for Spotswood High School, 1980, 3 Sheets (Box 26)
    Comm. #7629 D.T.
  - Bridgewater Office for the Rockingham National Bank, 1971, 18 Sheets (Box 27)
  - Various Rockingham County maps/plots, 7 Sheets (Box 27)
  - Rockingham Development Corporation, 1960, 29 Sheets (Box 27)
  - Warehouse Addition to Metro Pants Co., 1976, 5 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #7615
  - Exhibition Building for Rockingham County Fairgrounds, 1976, 12 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #7604
  - Addition to Steve Bradshaw's House--Massanutten Village, 1980, 10 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #8015
  - Bridgewater-Metro Metro Pants Co., 1968, 10 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #6841
  - Proposed Addition to Metro Pants, 1969, 8 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #6903
  - Bridgewater Intermediate School, 1965, 45 Sheets (Box 27)
    Comm. #6426
  - Proposed John C. Myers Junior High School, 1962, 4 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Metro Pants Distribution Center, 1976, 22 Sheets (Box 28)
  - C. W. Hertzler "Clinic"/Proposed Addition to Residence, 1958, 16 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Sunnyside Presbyterian Home Church/Chapel, 1958, 4 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Residence for Dr. & Mrs. Paul H. Bowman 1959, 38 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5909
  - Addition to Green Valley Clinic, 3 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5911
  - Manufacturing Plant Building for H. D. Lee Company Inc., 1960, 31 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5921
  - Sunnyside Cottage for Mr. & Mrs. Herbert Wood, 1966, 26 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #6532
  - Sunnyside Cottage No. 2 1967, 9 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #6702
  - Smith Residence 1978, 19 Sheets (Box 28)
  - Additions to R. D. C. Building #1, 1 Sheet (Box 28)
  - Fellowship Methodist Church, 1955, 25 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5516
  - Church of the Brethren, 1956, 17 Sheets (Box 28)
    Comm. #5603
  - Processing Plant for Rockingham Poultry Marketing Cooperative Inc., 1957, 2 Sheets (Box 28)